{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Lack of reaction to our own human leukocyte antigens (HLAs) is known as?", "opta": "autoimmunity", "optb": "complement system", "optc": "clonal selection", "optd": "tolerance", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following components of the vertebrate immune response occurs first upon invasion by a virus or bacterium?", "opta": "Activation of killer T lymphocytes", "optb": "Activation of B lymphocytes", "optc": "The inflammatory response", "optd": "Mobilization of complement proteins", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following white blood cells act as scavengers when they engulf and digest pathogens?", "opta": "Macrophages", "optb": "T cells", "optc": "B cells", "optd": "Lymphocytes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A cell which defends against body cells in which viruses are reproducing is", "opta": "Exotoxin", "optb": "Cytotoxic T cell", "optc": "Endotoxin", "optd": "Suppressor T cell", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is most likely to produce anaphylaxis in a susceptible individual?", "opta": "Pollen", "optb": "Mold", "optc": "Dust", "optd": "Bee sting", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What type of B cell remains dormant in the body, but can respond rapidly if the same antigen appears again?", "opta": "T cells", "optb": "Memory cells", "optc": "Plasma cells", "optd": "Macrophages", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The maturation of T cells and the production of particular T cell receptors occurs in the", "opta": "thyroid gland", "optb": "thymus gland", "optc": "testes", "optd": "all of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following provide specific defense against viruses and bacteria?", "opta": "T cells", "optb": "B cells", "optc": "Complement", "optd": "inflammation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of these is a type of specific defense against pathogens?", "opta": "Lymphocytes", "optb": "Macrophages", "optc": "Phagocytes", "optd": "Leukocytes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In animals, blood clots serve the function of", "opta": "consuming invading organisms", "optb": "helping them match the background coloration of the habitat", "optc": "stimulating production of killer T lymphocytes", "optd": "repairing damage to the body wall", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the result of invasion of a body by pathogens?", "opta": "Infection", "optb": "Inflammation", "optc": "Swelling", "optd": "Pus", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the behavior in which T cells and B cells constantly travel throughout the body seeking out and destroying foreign substances?", "opta": "Antibody-mediated immune response", "optb": "Immune surveillance", "optc": "Cell-mediated immune response", "optd": "Vaccination", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a fetus, where are lymphocytes produced?", "opta": "In the spleen", "optb": "In the bone marrow", "optc": "In the liver", "optd": "In the heart", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following produces the antibodies employed in the specific immune response of vertebrates?", "opta": "B lymphocytes", "optb": "T lymphocytes", "optc": "Neutrophils", "optd": "Macrophages", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not part of the vertebrate immune system?", "opta": "Lymphocytes", "optb": "Antibodies", "optc": "Cardiac glycosides", "optd": "Lymph nodes", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The protein, produced by B cells that binds to a specific antigen is", "opta": "phagocyte", "optb": "leukocyte", "optc": "vaccine", "optd": "antibody", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following characteristics are common in lymphocytes, macrophages, and neutrophils?", "opta": "They are all part of the nonspecific immune response in vertebrates", "optb": "They are all part of the specific immune response in vertebrates", "optc": "They are all part of the internal defenses of nonvertebrates", "optd": "They are all types of white blood cells", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following blood proteins can destroy pathogens?", "opta": "Major histocompatibility complex", "optb": "Platelets", "optc": "Fibrinogen", "optd": "Complement system", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of these is part of the lymphoid system in humans?", "opta": "Liver", "optb": "Stomach", "optc": "Tonsils", "optd": "Kidneys", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What type of B cell is like a tiny factory that produces antibodies identical to the B cell receptor that bind to the original antigen?", "opta": "T cells", "optb": "Memory cells", "optc": "Plasma cells", "optd": "Macrophages", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}